I think it's a great point.
And maybe I'll just bring
up,
we wanted to talk a little
bit about technology.
And I think that's a really
important part
of where we are going in
orthopedic surgery.
I'm part of a company on a
design team
that they're personalizing
implants,
they 3D print the implant
for you.
Can you imagine?
Yeah, so you imagine,
obviously, if you think that
something's made specialized
to you,
it might be a little bit
more tailored to you, your
anatomy, your size, and
hopefully
that would just sort of get
you in a better place,
better outcome back to the
gym fast
or whatever it is, but
that's where sort of the
technology's going.